## KIERAN WARWICK

Software Engineer ∼ Rungway

▼ me@kieranwarwick.dev kieranwarwick.dev

**\** 07446 861907 github.com/kw510

 London, UK in /in/kieran-warwick

#### **SUMMARY**

Product-driven software engineer. Master of Computer Science with First Class. Worked two startups, improving the scale and stability of their platforms. Main expertise is event-driven architecture using Go microservices, over gRPC. Considered a generalist programmer, with a lean to the theory of Computer Science.

**SKILLS** 

GoLang, TypeScript/JavaScript, JSX, SQL, Languages:

Python, Haskell, Java, C++, C, HTML, CSS,

PLEX.

Frontend: TSX/JSX, React, Mobx, Redux, Tailwind

Technology: GCP, Docker, gRPC, Microservices, K8s,

Pub/Sub. Kafka

#### **EXPERIENCE**

03/2023 -Present

## Software Engineer

· Lead the microsoft teams project. This enabled any of our clients to receive notifications via teams.

- · Architected events and notifications systems. Events are stored and used for event sourcing and auditing.
- · Built V3 from the ground up. Complete rewrite using product lead development. Allows for more scale, with lower running cost. Collaborated with key stakeholders to ensure product is as expected. / Go / gRPC / Pubsub / RabbitMQ / Java / React

11/2020 -03/2023

#### **Software Engineer**

Thirdfort

- · Developed and maintained new consistent authorisation system, Gatekeeper. Lead migration of the platform to this new system. Improved GET requests by 47%, to an average of 50ms.
- · Built and maintained Billing Engine, enabling operations to charge clients for exactly what they used on the platform. Added support for subscriptions that renew after a time frame.
- · Mentor and Coach. Provided insights to the team on RFCs and other technical discussions.
- · Worked with the cloud, CI/CD to the GCP K8 cluster, as well as managing Pub/Sub and Cloud Run.
- SRE member. Solved production issues. Fixed the root of them. / Go / gRPC / Pubsub / Kafka / Node / React

10/2017 -06/2018

## **Taught Academic Representative**

The University of Bath

· Negotiated upon the SSLC for higher marks for students who took a calculator exam paper, where a printing error caused no calculators to be provided.

10/2017 -06/2018

#### **Academic Peer Mentor**

The University of Bath

· Mentored a small group of first year students, helping them with their studies and adjusting to university.

**PROJECTS** 

# Technology

## protoc-gen-go-mock (protoc plugin)

Medium / Github

A tool that generates Go language bindings of services in protobuf definition files used for mocking gRPC in diffrent frameworks. Built because mocking gRPC frameworks should as easy as generating pb.go files.

Technology

## Analysis of Extended-Precision upon GPUs

Uses two floats to estimate a double, with arithmetic operations. Provides a speedup of up to 1.2 on consumer GPUs when compared to a native double. More speed, more precision, less range.

**EDUCATION** 

2016 - 2020 **Master of Computer Science**  University of Bath

Graduated with a First Class with Honours

2013 - 2016 A-Levels Maths: A\*, Further Maths: A, Physics A Chichester High Schools' Sixth Form

**GCSFs** 6As, 3Bs, 3Cs - including Maths & English **Chichester High School for Boys** 

**INTERESTS** 

2011 - 2013

Cycling, Coffee, Hackathons, Games, Technology, Blogging, F1.